

# DIMA OLEINIK

WEB-DEVELOPER

### **Contact**



Ukraine, Nikolaev



+380636371367



https://doleinik-portfolio.netlify.app



doleinika@gmail.com

### About Me

My name is Dima, I'm 24 years old.

Very purposeful and in a short time, thanks to his personal and professional qualities, he was able to achieve a good result, and I strive to learn more and more new technologies and develop in this.

### Education

### Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

2016 - 2020

MNU Sukhomlynsky

### Frontend Developer

2020 - 2020

BeetRoot Academy

## Master`s Degree, English Language and Literature

2022 - Present

MNU Sukhomlynsky

### **Work Experience**

Freelance

11.2020 - Present

Web developer

· Freelance website development

NextG

08.2021 - 11.2021

WordPress developer

- · Creation of sites from scratch
- · Support for written sites

Brightech

11.2021 - 07.2022

WordPress developer

- · Creation of sites from scratch
- · Support for written sites

Brightech

07.2022 - Present

**Team Lead/Tech Lead** 

WordPress developer

- · Creation of sites from scratch
- Support for written sites
- · Team management
- Trainee Internship
- · Quality control
- Mentoring

### ঞ্চ Skills

HTML/CSS Wordpress

Scss/Sass JavaScript

BEM PHP

•••••

Gulp Node.js

Gsap React

•••••

Three.js MySQL

•••••

## ᠅ WordPres plugin

. . . . . . .

. . . . . . .

ACF Pro Gravity forms

. . . . . . .

. . . . . . .

CF7 Elementor

Polylang Gutenberg

•••••

WPML Woocommerce

•••••

### **☑** Projects

**Panorama** 

**Americana Advisors** 

**Balard** 

**HedgeHog** 

**TillaDelse** 

**Hommondknol** 

**Senior services of america** 

**Brightech** 

**Freight Alliance** 

**Truit**